> > Brian Holt: 我们会做同样的事，但为了繁殖。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're gonna do
the same thing but for breed.
所以繁殖和 setBreed
So breed and setBreed and
我们只会让这个初始状态成为空的物体
we're just gonna make this initial
state to be an empty object.
> > Brian Holt: 然后它会看起来像动物一样。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then it's gonna
look really similar to animal.
因此在此标签下面，在 " 提交 " 按钮上方
So underneath this label here,
above the submit button,
我要说的是标签 htmlFor equals 品种
I'm gonna say label, htmlFor equals breed.
> > Brian Holt: 然后我们会说，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we're gonna say,
品种和其他选择。
breed and another select.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 接下来我们将在这个 id 的内部，平等地繁殖。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then here we're gonna
have inside of that id equals breed.
值 = 品种， >> Brian Holt: 来自它们，
Value = breed,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: From they're,
我们将会有 onChanged = e 返回 e.target.value 和
we're gonna have onChanged =
e returned e.target.value and
我们得把它放进 setBreed里面
we have to put that inside of setBreed.
>> Brian Holt: 那么对于 onBlur， onBlur
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then same thing for
onBlur, onBlur.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 还有一件事我们想做，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There's one
more thing we wanna do,
如果我换了， >> Brian Holt: 就像猫狗一样，对吧 ?
if I switch from,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Like cats to dogs, right?
他们有不同的品种所以我要不断刷新
They have different breeds so I have to
be constantly refreshing that list of
来反映目前的动物是什么样的，对吧 ?
breeds to reflective to of whatever
the current animal is, right?
所以我不能有一只狗猫我不能有一只小猫狗
So I can't have a poodle cat and
I can't have a tabby dog.
听起来很奇怪但你做不到对吧
That sounds weird but you can't, right?
所以有时它会在这些东西之间切换因为我要
So sometimes it'll be switching between
these things because I'm gonna have to be
不断地从 API中获取这些信息。
constantly getting that from the API.
所以我们要做的是当我给它一个残疾人
So what we're gonna do is
when I give it a disabled,
so disabled = breed.length.
所以如果 breed.length 是零，那么禁用它，对吗 ?
So if breed.length is zero,
then disable it, right?
那你就会想成为真正的人
Then you want that to be true.
您也可以执行此操作， breeds.length === 0，
You could also do this,
breeds.length === 0,
或者， >> Brian Holt: 是。
or,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah.
>> Brian Holt: 我们将在这里定义品种，仅在第二种情况下，它还不存在。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We'll define breeds here in
just a second, cuz that doesn't exist yet.
但这是有意义的
But does this make sense, and
另一件事就是他说的另一个连字
the other thing this is another
ligature that was talking about.
它是三种不同的等号，但它是放在一起的。
It's three different equal signs,
but it's put together.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，现在将始终禁用此操作，如人员将
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now this will
always be disabled, like people will
如果 breed.length 为 0，那么无法单击它。
not be able to click on
it if breed.length is 0.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，然后我们再做一件事
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
then we're gonna do another thing where
您可以选择所有这些项。
you can select all of them.
所以我要说选项， >> Brian Holt: 所有和
So I'm gonna say option,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: All and
然后我们就会有另一个这样的
then underneath that, we're going
to have another one of these for
在那里会有繁殖的循环或地图
loops or
maps up there which is gonna be breeds.
同样地，我们将在这里定义一个第二，
Again, which we'll define here in
just a second, .map(breed, and
然后返回该选项。
then return for that an option.
>> Brian Holt: 在此选项中，我们会进行繁殖。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
inside of that option we'll have breed.
让我们称之为不同于犬种的东西，这会让人困惑。
Let's actually call this something
different than breed cuz that's confusing.
这就像是> > Brian Holt: Breed 字符串或
This would be like,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Breed string or
就像这样
something like that.
>> Brian Holt: 繁殖字符串，像这样的品种串。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So breed string,
breed string like that.
我们得把钥匙和钥匙
And we have to get that as well the key
的字符串和 reedString的值。
of breed string and value of breedString.
>> Brian Holt: 这跟上面差不多。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's
pretty similar to above.
再一次，我们会在第二个物种中确定品种，但我会让你把它抓起来。
Again, we'll define breed in just
a second, but I'll let you catch that up.
好了过来到上面来
Okay, so come back up here to the top.
还有下面的品种和 breedString
Also underneath breed and breedString,
我们还得追踪品种和 setBreeds
we're also gonna have to keep
track of breeds and setBreeds.
>> Brian Holt: 然后，初始状态将为空数组，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then it's initial
state is gonna be an empty array, right?
因为我们要像养狗一样反对宣传声带
Because we're gonna be requesting
against the APIs like I have a dog,
把所有的狗种都还给我
give me back all of the dog breeds.
因此，这会根据用户选择的内容而不断变化。
So this is gonna be constantly changing
depending on what the user is selecting.
>> Brian Holt: 这是否有意义 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Does that make sense?
所以现在，狗只会是一个空虚的数组。
So for now,
breeds is just gonna be an empty array.
所以不管怎么说如果你去看这里
So no matter what,
if you go look over here,
你就会发现它总是被禁用的
you'll just see that it's always disabled.
因为我们从不改变这一切
And set to all because
we're never changing that.